goamp.com 2004-12-07

# AMP - Privacy Statement

|  |  | 

Privacy Statement

This Applied Measurement Professional's, Inc. ( **AMP** ) privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for goamp.com. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we are disclosing our information practices: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personal identification is collected from you through the web site.
  2. The organization collecting the information.
  3. How the information is used.
  4. With whom the information may be shared.
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under AMP's control.
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you feel that we are not abiding by our posted privacy policy, you should first contact the Chief Information Officer [by email](mailto:AMPCIO@goAMP.com?subject=) or by phone at 843.520.2992.

**Information Collection and Use**   
AMP is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We may collect information from you at several different points on our website.  
**  
Site Registration**  
In order to use portions of our website, you must first complete one or more registration forms. During registration you are required to give your contact information (e.g., name and e-mail address). This information is to provide you with the services on our site for which you have expressed interest. Certain other demographic information is identified as optional. The type of service you are using affects the types of information you are requested, or required, to provide.

**Online Store**  
We request information from you when purchasing through our online store. You must provide contact information (e.g., name and shipping address) and financial information (e.g., credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your order. If we have trouble processing your order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you. We also capture certain information about your Internet connection (e.g., IP address) to assist us maintain site security and to help us protect against fraudulent use.

**Web Tests**  
On our site we offer online tests that may be purchased through our online store. We host some of these tests for third party organizations. These web tests may require you to provide unique information (e.g., Social Security number) to control access to the test. If such information is required, it is used solely for the purpose of the examination process and is not disclosed for any other purpose. In some instances, online exams provide score results to you via e-mail. These score results are also typically provided to the third party providing the test and may be provided to other parties (e.g., an instructor). Additionally, test scores are maintained on AMP servers for varying periods of time or until the examination is no longer offered. If you have any questions or concerns regarding the disposition of score information, you should contact the provider of the examination. Contact information for each examination is provided in the confirming e-mail when the examination is ordered.

**High Stakes Examination Registration and Scheduling**  
On our site we offer online registration and scheduling of high-stakes examinations administered in one of our affiliated test centers. Registration for these examinations may require you to provide unique information (e.g., Social Security number) to identify you and to verify your eligibility to take the examination. If such information is required, it is used solely for the purpose of the examination process and is not disclosed for any other purpose. This information is also typically provided to the third party sponsoring the examination (e.g., a state or national board). When you take the examination at one of our testing centers or testing locations, examination scores are recorded, transmitted to AMP servers, stored for varying periods of time, and made available to the sponsoring organization. If you have any questions or concerns regarding the disposition of your information, you should contact AMP or the provider of the examination.  

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, your logon ID would be remembered for the next time you visit our site. If you reject a cookie, you may be limited in some areas of our site. For example, you will not be able to participate in any of our web tests. Cookies can also enable us to track and target your interests to enhance the experience on our site. 

**Log Files**  
We also use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track your movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**Sharing**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use a credit card processing company to bill you for products and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When you sign up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We may also disclose certain information with legal counsel or with officers of the court when required or needed.

**Links**  
Our web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

**Newsletters and Mailing Lists**  
If you choose to subscribe to our newsletter or mailing list, we ask you for contact information such as name and e-mail address. We do provide a method for you to be removed from the newsletter or mailing list.

**Surveys**  
From time-to-time our site may request information from you via surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (e.g., name and shipping address), and demographic information (e.g., zip code and age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our site.

**Security**  
Our website takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When we ask you to enter sensitive information (e.g., credit card number and/or Social Security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the industry standard encryption software known as SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer indicates as closed lock. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also take prudent measures to protect your information off-line. All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing and customer service staffs) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, we strive to keep all employees up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an [email to us.](mailto:info@goAMP.com?subject=) It is important to note that you also play a significant role in protecting your information. We take precautions to ensure that no one can view or edit your personal information on our website without knowing your password, so do not share your password with others.

It is important to note that you also play a significant role in protecting your information. We take precautions to ensure that no one can view or edit your personal information on our web site without knowing your password, so do not share your password with others.

**Protection of Children’s Personal Information**  
We do not publish content that is targeted to children.

**Special Offers**  
We send new users a welcoming e-mail to verify password and username. You will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, newsletters and the like. Respecting your privacy, we always present an option for you to not receive these types of communications. Please see "Choice/Opt-Out" below.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes (e.g., your zip code), or if you no longer desire our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data provided to us UNLESS the data you have provided is under the auspices of a client for whom we are required to maintain long-term information for examination, licensure or credentialing purposes.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
You are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your information used for purposes not directly related to our site. This is typically done at the point where we ask for the information. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners you may opt-out of receiving these communications by responding to the opt-out instructions in the e-mail. Or, [email us for more information.](mailto:info@goAMP.com?subject=Privacy%20Statement%20Information%20Request)

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will attempt to notify you by way of an e-mail.

Updated on 31-Jan-20   
[Terms of Use](http://www.goamp.com/AMP/Termsofuse.htm) | [Privacy  
](http://www.goamp.com/AMP/Privacystatement.htm)Lost? Try the sitemap. **  
© 2004 Applied Measurement Professionals, Inc.**

|
